everyblock.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Local Media Development

**Summary**

**What the Privacy Policy does**  
These Terms set forth the terms and conditions through which Comcast will permit you to use the Local Media Development sites as well as Comcast-owned and operated websites and services based on the POV and EveryBlock platform (the **“Web Services“** ). A list of such websites can we found at http://comcastlmd.com (the **“Web Services“** ).

**What the Privacy Policy does not do**  
Please note: the Privacy Policy does not tell you what information we collect and how we use it when you use other Comcast services (Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand, Comcast Digital Voice, Comcast High Speed Internet, XFINITY TV, XFINITY Voice, or XFINITY Internet). These websites and services have their own privacy policies, which we post at <http://xfinity.comcast.net/privacy/2013-06/> for the websites and web services and at <http://www.comcast.com/customerprivacy/> and by mail to subscribers for other Comcast services.

**The Information Comcast Collects and How It is Used and Shared**  
We want you to understand what kinds of information may be collected about your use of the Websites and Web Services, and what we might do with that information.

Comcast collects two types of information from people who use its Websites: (i) information that identifies a particular person using a Website, and (ii) information that provides facts about a person without identifying him or her.

**Information that Identifies Someone**  
Information that identifies a particular person could be a name, address or email address, for example. We will not make this information public or share this information with another website or company, unless you tell us to (for example, if you want to use social networking sites such as Twitter and Facebook to post information on the Local Media Development Web Services, or you want to post information from the Local Media Development Web Services on a social network.). When you post content on the Local Media Development Web Services, and use your username, it may not identify you by itself, but if it is linked to a profile you have created in which you have included personally identifiable information, then the user name may also be used to identify you, and you should be aware of that when you use your user name to post to the sites.

We also use this kind of identifying information to provide services to you. For example, we may use it to confirm your identity when you login, or to communicate with you. Sometimes we use other companies to help us provide our services. We may share your information with these companies, but they are required to protect it and to use it only to help us provide services to you. These service providers are not allowed to use the information for any other purpose themselves.

**Information that Does Not Identify a Specific Person**  
Information that does not identify a person could be a non-personal record of online activity, or information you put in a profile – like your zip code, your age or your gender (when it’s used without your name). We routinely collect this kind of information and use it to improve your experience, -for example, by showing you content that may be more relevant and interesting to someone like you. Sometimes we share this kind of non-personal information with other companies that help us deliver and improve our services.

**Your Information May be Shared Among Comcast Companies**  
The Web Services are provided by various companies that are part of, or affiliated with, Comcast. We may share your information with Comcast ([http://www.comcast.com](http://www.comcast.com/ "Comcast")) and its web sites ([http://xfinity.comcast.net](http://xfinity.comcast.net/ "Xfinity")) so we can make it easier for you to use several Web Services seamlessly. Also, if you use the Web Services in connection with other Comcast services (for example, to set your DVR online to record a show on your television), we may need to share your information with the Comcast companies that offer those services, too.

**Disclosure of your Information**  
We respect and protect your privacy, but it is possible that we may be required to provide information about you to a court or law enforcement agency. We will only disclose your information if we are legally required to do so—if we receive a valid subpoena, court order, or search warrant, for example.

**Your Choices**  
We want you to know how you can control the personal information that we may collect. When you use the Web Services that post the Privacy Policy, you are agreeing that the policy applies to you.

**Online Tracking Policy**  
Some of the third party service providers that Comcast uses to deliver services, content and advertising may collect information on this website, as disclosed in this privacy policy. This information may include personally identifiable information or may be used to contact you online.

Comcast is participating in the World Wide Web Consortium’s (W3C) process to develop a “Do Not Track” Standard. Since the definitions and rules for such a standard have not yet been defined, Comcast does not yet respond to “Do Not Track” signals sent from browsers.

You may opt out of receiving cookies from companies that provide services on this website by going to <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>. You may opt out of receiving promotional email or direct mail from Comcast based on your visits to this website by going to our Preference Center at [www.comcast.com/preferences](http://www.comcast.com/preferences) and following the instructions there.

**Registering**  
You may choose not to register for any one of the Web Services (or for all of them) if you do not want to share information that identifies you when you use that Website.

If you do register, we will give you a chance to create a profile. We may use some of the information in that profile, such as the neighborhood you have chosen, to choose the content we think you would like to see.

When you register, we may also send you email about other products and services. You may choose not to receive these messages. However, we will still send you email with information about the specific services you use.

Children under 13 may not create profiles that include personally identifiable information.

**Blogs and Forums**  
If you choose to post information on blogs or forums, it will not be private. Once the information is posted, other users may copy or store it. You must use a user name to post information the Local Media Development Web Services.

**Transferring Information to Social Networking Sites and Services**  
You may choose to use social networking websites to share information from your Web Services profile, or information about what you do when you use the Web Services. If we get instructions to send your information to one of these websites, with your valid Web Services login information included, we will accept the instructions to transfer your information.

**Changes to Comcast’s Business or the Privacy Policy**  
If Comcast’s business changes—for example, if our company merges with another company or we sell one or more of the Comcast companies that provide the Web Services—we may give the new owners of the Web Services your information. If this happens, or if the Privacy Policy changes for any other reason, we will post a notice on the Privacy Policy so you can decide whether you want to continue using the Web Services <http://essayswriters.biz/>.

**Full Policy**

  1. **About the Privacy Policy and the Web Services**

The Comcast family of companies respects your privacy. Within this Web Services Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy“) the term “Comcast” or “we” will refer to Comcast Cable Communications Management, LLC, and its respective subsidiaries and affiliates that own and operate Websites and Internet services on their behalf. The term “you” refers to you as a user of Comcast’s Websites or Internet services described below.

The term “Personally Identifiable Information” or “PII” refers to information that identifies a specific person, such as the person’s name, address, email address, or social network login. The term “Non-Personally Identifiable Information” or “non-PII” refers to information that is demographic, aggregated, or does not otherwise identify a specific person, such as a person’s age, gender, ZIP code, or other information when that information is not used with Personally Identifiable Information. A user name does not necessarily identify you, but if you include personally identifiable information in the profile you post, and the user name links to the profile, then it too becomes personally identifiable information.

**What does this Privacy Policy cover?**  
This Privacy Policy explains how Comcast will use the information that you provide when you use the Comcast-owned and operated Websites and services that are party of Local Media Development. The full list of Websites and services is viewable at [http://comcastlmd.com](http://comcastlmd.com/ "Comcast Local Media Development") (the **“Web Services“** ).

**What is outside the scope of this Privacy Policy?**  
This Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of any other products or services provided by Comcast such as Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand, Comcast Digital Voice, Comcast High Speed Internet, XFINITY TV, XFINITY Voice, or XFINITY Internet. If you subscribe to or use one or more of these services, you can see the privacy policy that applies to the residential versions of these services by visiting <http://www.comcast.com/customerprivacy/>.

This Privacy Policy also does not apply to Comcast’s use of information provided by you when you sign up for or use the XFINITY TV Store (xfinitytvstore.comcast.net). Comcast’s use of the information you provide through the XFINITY TV Store is described in the XFINITY TV Store Privacy Policy, available at [http://xfinitytvstore.comcast.net/PrivacyPolicy.aspx](http://xfinitytvstore.comcast.net/PrivacyPolicy.aspx.).

Some of the Web Services contain links to other Websites, including Websites of third parties who are acting on our behalf as our agents, suppliers, or providers. These other Websites are not operated by Comcast and have their own privacy policies that we encourage you to read before you use them. Other sites that we link to may contain Comcast branding, but these non-Comcast Websites and resources are provided by companies or persons other than Comcast. Examples of these non-Comcast Websites include Websites where you are required to log-in using a username and password other than your username and password for the Web Services This Privacy Policy does not apply to those non-Comcast owned Web Services. Those sites will have their own policies that we encourage you to read before you use them.

  2. **Collection of Information**

**All Users**  
Comcast, and third parties acting on Comcast’s behalf, routinely log Non-Personally Identifiable Information that is automatically generated when all users visit or use the Web Services, as a by-product of the user’s activities (“Web Log Data“). This information includes, but is not limited to, Internet protocol (“IP“) header information that is automatically passed between a user’s computer and the Web Services, such as the computer’s IP address, the browser being used at the time, and the URL of the webpage on the Web Services that the browser requested. This information may also include details relating to the activities users perform within the Web Services, such as what links they click on, in what order they access specific web pages within the Web Services, and the search queries they perform on the Web Services.

Some of the Web Services allow you to store certain details and preferences that help you personalize that service (“Preference Data“). This Non-Personally Identifiable Information may include ZIP code, age and gender. Comcast may store Preference Data in a cookie and place it on your computer. We do this so that you do not have to enter this data every time you return to the Web Services. We may also use the Preference Data to deliver other personalized services and features of the Web Services.

**Registered Users**  
Comcast asks you to provide certain information when you initially register to use the Web Services and then afterwards may ask you to provide additional information when you use certain Web Services for the first time. In addition, Comcast also collects information about your use of the Web Services as a registered user. This table summarizes the different types of information that we may collect from you when you register for the Web Services and use the Web Services as a registered user.

    * **Registration Data** : 
      * When Collected: When you create an account for the Web Services or subsequently modify your Registration Data
      * Representative Examples: email address, user name, password and zip code, as well as user names and password from sites you wish to link to your account (i.e. Twitter, Facebook, etc.)
    * **Profile Data**
      * When Collected: The first time you access certain Web Services after you have created an account or subsequently modify your Profile Data
      * Representative Examples: Additional e-mail addresses, social network username, lists of people to connect with through certain EveryBlock or POV Web Services, and notification preferences
    * **Activity Data**
      * When Collected: When you log-in to your account and use the Web Services
      * Representative Examples: Flagging or rating content, posting comments, sharing URLs, and content and data feeds from non-Comcast social networks or services

Collectively, your Registration Data, Profile Data, Activity Data, and any other generally available demographic data about you that Comcast gathers from other sources is referred to as “Your Data.” Your Data does not include information that third parties may independently gather from other Websites about you using their own cookies, as further described in this Privacy Policy.  
Most Web Services have their own pages where you can manage certain portions of your Registration Data and Profile Data relevant to that specific site.

  3. **Online Tracking Policy**

Some of the third party service providers that Comcast uses to deliver services, content and advertising may collect information on this website, as disclosed in this privacy policy. This information may include personally identifiable information or may be used to contact you online.

Comcast is participating in the World Wide Web Consortium’s (W3C) process to develop a “Do Not Track” Standard. Since the definitions and rules for such a standard have not yet been defined, Comcast does not yet respond to “Do Not Track” signals sent from browsers.

You may opt out of receiving cookies from companies that provide services on this website by going to [http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp) You may opt out of receiving promotional email or direct mail from Comcast based on your visits to this website by going to our Preference Center at [www.comcast.com/preferences](http://www.comcast.com/preferences) and following the instructions there.

  4. **Use of Information**

Comcast uses Web Log Data, Preferences Data, and Your Data, including both Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information in both aggregated and individual forms, to provide the Web Services and support them. We may process and use this data for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy including, but not limited to:

    * Customize, measure, and improve the Web Services, and the content provided through them;
    * Enforce our Web Services Terms of Service and detect fraud and other illegal activities;
    * Let you know about changes to the Web Services, the Web Services Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy, and other terms that apply to our services; and
    * Update any programs or other tools that we provide in conjunction with the Web Services.

Comcast may use Web Log Data, Preferences Data, and Your Data in these forms for internal business purposes, such as determining how much traffic certain portions of the Web Services receive, for license reporting and assessment of service levels, to better understand how the Web Services are used, to gauge traffic patterns and determine what types of content and services are most popular with users of the Web Services, or determining which search queries are the most popular.

Comcast may also use Web Log Data, Preferences Data, and Your Data to customize the Web Services and Services and make them more relevant to you. For example, Comcast may use such data to determine which channels, content, events, discussions or projects to recommend to you.

Comcast may use your Registration Data to verify that you are the person authorized to use the Web Services or to manage your account. Comcast may also use your Registration Data to determine whether your Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand subscription allows you to access premium content or services offered through some of the Web Services. For example, Comcast may use this subscription information to permit you to access, via one or more of the Web Services or certain programming included in your Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand package.

  5. **Sharing of Information**

Comcast uses third parties to assist us in delivering parts of the Web Services to you. We may share portions of Your Data with these third parties to the extent necessary for them to provide these services. These companies are acting on Comcast’s behalf and are required, by contract with Comcast, to keep this information confidential and are only authorized to use it for specific purposes on our behalf. As described in more detail below, Comcast may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information elements of Your Data to third parties who deliver ads to you on Comcast’s behalf. Comcast will not provide your Personally Identifiable Information to these advertisers unless you expressly authorize us to do so.

Comcast may also share Web Log Data and Preference Data, which do not contain Personally Identifiable Information, with third parties. For example, Comcast may share traffic data for one of the Web Services with a third party that analyzes and publishes Website traffic surveys. Or, Comcast may share Web Log Data and Preference Data with the content providers to the Web Services.  
Comcast may also share Web Log Data, Preference Data, and Your Data within its internal family of companies solely to provide you with the Web Services or other cross-platform services it thinks may be of interest to you.

You may authorize other Internet sites such as Twitter or Facebook to access and publish on their Websites some of Your Data, including your Activity Data. In addition, certain Web Services allow you to use your contact lists from Internet sites such as Twitter or Facebook to share portions of Your Data, including your Activity Data, with others. If you provide Comcast with your credentials for this kind of Internet service and use the features of the Web Services that share information across these Internet services, or, if one of these Internet service contacts Comcast using your Web Services credentials and asks to have access to certain portions of Your Data, Comcast will treat this as your authorization to share such portions of Your Data with that Internet service.

  6. **Communicating with You**

Comcast may use your Registration Data to send you a confirmation e-mail verifying the ownership of the e-mail addresses provided in your Registration Data and to send you service-related communications about the Web Services. In addition, Comcast may send you promotional e-mail relating to the Web Services for which you have activated your account as permitted by applicable law. You can opt-out from receiving such promotional e-mail by following the instructions contained in the e-mails or individual website.

  7. Participating in Blogs and Forums

If you post comments to any of the blogs, forums, or other community sections of the Web Services, any information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of the Web Services and any PII you post could be used to contact you. We are not responsible for PII you choose to submit through these features.

Children under the age of 13 should not post in any of the blogs, forums, or other editorial sections of the Web Services.

  8. **Security**

Comcast uses industry standard approaches to securely store, control access to, and make appropriate use of Your Data, and we require our contractors and other providers to do so as well. However, no security measure is completely effective and Comcast cannot guarantee the complete security of Your Data. If you don’t want Comcast to know any particular information about you, you should not register to use the Web Services or include it in anything that you submit or post to Comcast, including posts on the Web Services or e-mails to Comcast.

As an additional security precaution, neither Comcast nor any of our authorized service providers will ask you for your Comcast password in an e-mail, over the telephone, or in an online support forum or chat area. **Do not give your password to anyone in an e-mail, over the telephone, or in an online support area**.

  9. **Disclosures of Information**

Comcast holds customer privacy in the highest regard and we make every reasonable effort to protect your privacy as described in this Privacy Policy. Nevertheless, we may be required by law to disclose Personally Identifiable Information or other information about you or other users of the Web Services. These disclosures may be made with or without your consent, and with or without notice, in compliance with the terms of a subpoena, court order, search warrant, or other valid legal process. We may also disclose information about you or users of the Web Services when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent financial loss, address suspected illegal activity, protect our rights or property, or prevent imminent physical harm.

  10. **Special Note About Children**

Comcast does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from anyone under the age of 13 without first obtaining parental consent. If any portions of the Web Services do seek to collect information from children under the age of 13 after obtaining parental consent, we will provide a special notice or other information describing any additional privacy protections that may apply. Children should always get permission from a parent or legal guardian before sending or posting any information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses, and telephone numbers) over the Internet, to Comcast or to anyone else.

  11. **Your California Privacy Rights**

California law permits its residents to request and receive information about a business’ disclosure of certain categories of PII to other companies for their use for direct marketing. If you are a California resident and a user of any of the Web Services, you can request a copy of this information from Comcast_Web_Privacy at Comcast dot com or a letter to Comcast Cable Communications Management, LLC, Attn: California Direct Marketing Information, One Comcast Center, Philadelphia, PA 19103. Please include your name and e-mail address in e-mail requests, and your name and postal address in mail requests.

  12. **Change of Ownership or Other Business Transaction**

In the event Comcast enters into a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or the sale of all or part of its assets (a **“Business Transition“** ), Your Data (including PII and non-PII associated with the Web Services) will likely be part of the assets transferred.

In this event, we will notify you of any Business Transition. We will also notify you of any subsequent material changes to this Privacy Policy as a result of a Business Transaction and give you the opportunity to opt-out for information that we have collected before, or may collect after, a new Privacy Policy containing material changes takes effect.

  13. **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Comcast reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time consistent with applicable privacy laws. When we do change it, we will make a copy of the updated Privacy Policy available to you before it takes effect. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will also notify you by e-mail, direct mail, or other reasonable methods that we select. In the event of material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will give you the opportunity to opt-out for information that we have collected before, or may collect after, a new Privacy Policy containing material changes takes effect.

You understand and agree that if you use the Web Services after the effective date of the updated Privacy Policy, Comcast will consider your use as acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy.

  14. **International Visitors**

Our computer systems are currently based in the United States, so your PII will be processed by us in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may be different than other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create an online account to use the Web Services as a visitor from outside the United States, you will have agreed to the terms of the Privacy Policy and our Web Services Terms of Service and you will have consented to the transfer to and processing of all such information in the United States, which many not offer an equivalent level of protection of that in the European Union or certain other countries.

  15. **Contacting Comcast & Customer Support**

You can direct questions regarding this Privacy Policy to Comcast by e-mailing us at Comcast_Web_Privacy at Comcast dot com. You can also send a letter by mail to Comcast Cable Communications Management, LLC, Attn: Web Services Privacy Policy Questions, One Comcast Center, Philadelphia, PA 19103 USA

**Effective: January 23, 2014**
